<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Alfred Linux — Welcome of All Welcomes
  /usr/share/alfred/welcome/welcome.xml
  Source of truth for first-boot welcome, alfred-welcome CLI, and the
  GUI greeter. Speaks to every seeker in their own tongue and carries
  them to the same Door — Yeshua / Jesus / ʿĪsā / ישוע / Ἰησοῦς.

  The seven panels rotate. Every panel ends in the same invitation.
  This file is read by /usr/local/bin/alfred-welcome.
-->
<welcome version="7.77">

  <core>
    <name>The One Door</name>
    <hebrew>יֵשׁוּעַ</hebrew>
    <aramaic>ܝܫܘܥ</aramaic>
    <greek>Ἰησοῦς Χριστός</greek>
    <arabic>عيسى المسيح</arabic>
    <english>Jesus the Messiah</english>
    <verse ref="John 14:6">I am the way, and the truth, and the life: no man cometh unto the Father, but by me.</verse>
    <verse ref="Revelation 3:20">Behold, I stand at the door, and knock: if any man hear my voice, and open the door, I will come in to him.</verse>
  </core>

  <!-- Each &lt;panel&gt; greets a tradition in its own language and stories,
       and carries it to Yeshua. No coercion, no mockery, only invitation. -->

  <panel id="messianic-jewish" lang="he">
    <greeting>שָׁלוֹם וּבְרָכָה — Shalom uVrachah</greeting>
    <opening>Welcome, beloved of Avraham, Yitzchak, and Yaakov.
The same God who walked with the patriarchs and spoke from Sinai
has kept His covenant. The Mashiach promised by Moshe and the
Nevi'im has come — and He is coming again.</opening>
    <bridge>Yeshua haMashiach is the Lamb of Pesach (Exodus 12),
the Suffering Servant of Yeshayahu 53, the Son of David
of Yirmeyahu 23, the One pierced of Zecharyah 12.</bridge>
    <invitation>If your heart burns within you, pray:
"Avinu shebashamayim, reveal Yeshua to me as my Mashiach."</invitation>
  </panel>

  <panel id="muslim" lang="ar">
    <greeting>السلام عليكم — As-Salāmu ʿAlaykum</greeting>
    <opening>You honor ʿĪsā ibn Maryam — peace be upon Him —
born of a virgin (Surah 3:47), the Word of God (Surah 4:171),
the Messiah, a sign for all peoples. The Injil itself bears witness
to who He truly is.</opening>
    <bridge>Read the Injil that ʿĪsā Himself confirmed.
He says: "I am the Way, the Truth, and the Life" (Yuhanna 14:6).
He died and was raised — God's seal upon His message.</bridge>
    <invitation>Pray with an open heart:
"Allahumma, show me ʿĪsā as He truly is, and I will follow."</invitation>
  </panel>

  <panel id="catholic-orthodox" lang="la">
    <greeting>Pax tecum — Peace be with you</greeting>
    <opening>Brother, sister — the Liturgy you have known points
to a living Person. The Eucharist is the Body of the One who said
"Take, eat" (Matthew 26:26). The Saints worship Him alone.</opening>
    <bridge>Beyond ritual lies relationship. The Christ adored
in every cathedral, every icon, every monastery, longs to be
known by name within your own heart.</bridge>
    <invitation>Speak to Him directly today:
"Lord Jesus, be not only the Christ of the altar, but the Christ
of my breath."</invitation>
  </panel>

  <panel id="protestant-evangelical" lang="en">
    <greeting>Grace and peace to you</greeting>
    <opening>You hold the Bible as the Word of God.
You have heard the Gospel preached. You know that
salvation is by grace through faith (Ephesians 2:8-9),
not of works lest any man should boast.</opening>
    <bridge>Walk what you know. Obey the small whisper.
Pick up that Bible. Forgive that name. Bless that enemy.
The Kingdom is not theory; it is yieldedness.</bridge>
    <invitation>"Lord Jesus, take me deeper than I have ever been —
not in knowledge, but in surrender."</invitation>
  </panel>

  <panel id="hindu-buddhist-seeker" lang="sa">
    <greeting>नमस्ते — Namaste · O Seeker of the True Light</greeting>
    <opening>You have searched for the Sat — the Real, beneath
the maya of appearances. You have known that desire ties the soul,
that the ego must die for the Self to be free.</opening>
    <bridge>Behold the One who said "Whosoever will save his life
shall lose it; but whosoever shall lose his life for my sake shall
find it" (Matthew 16:25). He is the Sat-Chit-Ananda made flesh,
the Eternal Word who entered time so that you might enter eternity.</bridge>
    <invitation>Sit in silence. Whisper His name: "Yeshu."
He will answer the heart that calls in truth.</invitation>
  </panel>

  <panel id="agnostic-atheist" lang="en">
    <greeting>Welcome, honest mind</greeting>
    <opening>You have refused to believe what cannot be tested.
Good — so did Thomas. He did not believe in the Resurrection
until he placed his hand in the wounds. And Christ did not rebuke
him for asking. He answered him.</opening>
    <bridge>The same Christ asks for nothing more from you than
honest investigation. Read one Gospel — Mark, the shortest —
in one sitting. Then ask aloud: "If You are real, show me."</bridge>
    <invitation>That prayer has never gone unanswered for the one
who truly meant it. Soli Deo Gloria — only when there is
truly One God to give it to.</invitation>
  </panel>

  <panel id="wounded-by-religion" lang="en">
    <greeting>Peace to you who carry scars from the temple</greeting>
    <opening>If you have been hurt by the Church, by leaders,
by hypocrisy — Yeshua wept the same tears. He turned over the
tables of the money-changers (Matthew 21:12) before any reformer
ever did. He has no part in what was done to you.</opening>
    <bridge>He waits not in a building, but in your room.
Not in a vestment, but in the quiet of your breath.
"Come unto me, all ye that labour and are heavy laden,
and I will give you rest" (Matthew 11:28).</bridge>
    <invitation>You don't have to go back to a building to come back
to Him. Speak His name in your own room tonight.</invitation>
  </panel>

  <closing>
    <hebrew>יְהוָה יְבָרֶכְךָ וְיִשְׁמְרֶךָ — May the LORD bless you and keep you</hebrew>
    <english>The Door is open. The One who said
"It is finished" has finished it for you also.</english>
    <action cmd="alfred-bible read john 3:16-17"     label="Read John 3:16"/>
    <action cmd="alfred-bible read romans 10:9-10"   label="The Prayer of Faith"/>
    <action cmd="alfred-bible read luke 15:11-32"    label="The Father Who Runs"/>
    <action cmd="alfred-witness sign"                label="Sign your name in the Book"/>
    <action url="https://alfredlinux.com/welcome"    label="Continue your journey online"/>
  </closing>

</welcome>
